invisiblehand.co.uk 2009-02-19

# 

Welcome to InvisibleHand.co.uk (the “Site”) brought to You by Forward Internet Group Limited. We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to InvisibleHand.co.uk. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that You provide to us. 

  1. Contacting Invisible Hand  1.1 |  Invisible Hand is brought to You by Forward Internet Group Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales. If you want to know what information we hold about you or if you have any other queries in relation to this privacy policy, please contact us using the following information: 

Postal Address:  
Forward Internet Group Limited,  
1 Conduit Street,  
London, W1S 2XA

Email: info@invisiblehand.co.uk  
---|---  
  2. Information That We Collect From You  2.1 | In the future, when You register with InvisibleHand.co.uk, You will be asked to provide Your name, an email address and a password. By registering, You consent to the collection, use and transfer of Your information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We may also collect information about Your usage of the Site, as well as information about You, from e-mails or letters that You send to us. We will only use any such information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.  
---|---  
2.2 | Any materials or information that You post to the Site may be visible to other users of the Site and is stored on our servers for the purposes of making the Site available, we do not collect any personal information contained in any such post or store it for any other purpose. We advise You to be selective about what information You post on the Site or that You provide to other users. Please do not include the following information in any post to a discussion forum: telephone numbers, addresses, surname etc.  
2.3 | We may receive some information that you submit to any third party website that you access from a link contained in the Site. Both us and the owner or operator of that third party Site will be the data controller in respect of any such information and You should check the privacy policy of that site to find out how they will use your data. We will only use that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
2.4 | We may collect generic information about how the Site is used, the location of our users based on their IP addresses. Individual users will not be identifiable from this information and we may use this information for a number of purposes such as optimising the use of the Site, disclosing to advertisers or third party contributors, security purposes.  
  3. Use Of Your Information  3.1 | We will only use Your information for the following purposes: 
    1. to administer Your account and enable us to provide You with access to all parts of the Site and to enable You to download information and materials from the Site;
    2. to enable us to provide You with the services that you have subscribed to from the Site and to ensure compliance with the Terms of Use;
    3. to provide customer service in relation to Your use of the Site; and
    4. to administer, support, improve and develop our Site.  
---|---  
  4. Disclosure Of Your Information  4.1 | Other than as expressly set out in this privacy policy or as otherwise required or permitted by law, we will not share, sell or distribute any of the information You provide to us without Your consent.  
---|---  
4.2 | You should therefore be careful when submitting information about Yourself and only submit information that You are happy to be public information.  
4.3 | We may disclose Your personal information to (i) any third party to whom disclosure is necessary to enable Us to provide You with any service to which You have subscribed via the Site, (ii) any person to whom disclosure is necessary to enable Us to enforce Our rights under this privacy policy or under the Terms of Use, (iii) any holding company or subsidiary of Forward Internet Group Limited, (iv) any purchaser of any of the assets or undertaking of Forward Internet Group Limited or any purchaser of the Site .  
  5. Cookies  5.1 | InvisibleHand.co.uk uses cookies to ensure that You get the most out of the Site. Cookies are small amounts of information that we store on Your computer and they make it easier for You to log on to and use the Site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and when appropriate, to personalise the content of the Site for You. If you do not wish us to install cookies on Your computer for these purposes, You may change the settings on Your internet browser to reject cookies. For more information please consult the “Help” section of your browser. Please note that if You do set your browser to reject cookies, You may not be able to use all of the features of our Site.  
---|---  
  6. Third Party Sites and Contributors  6.1 | The Site contains links to websites and microsites that are operated by third parties. We do not control those websites and microsites and as such this privacy policy does not apply to those websites and microsites. Please consult the terms and conditions and privacy policy of those third party websites and microsites to find out how they collect and use Your personal data and to establish whether and for what purpose they use cookies.   
---|---  
6.2 | Advertisements contained on our Site operate as links to that advertiser’s websites and as such any information they collect by virtue of Your clicking on that link will be collected and used in accordance with the privacy policy of that advertiser.  
  7. Security And Data Retention  7.1 | We employ security measures to protect Your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain Your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires or permits.  
---|---  
  8. Your Rights  8.1 | You are entitled to see the information held about You and You may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If You wish to do this, please contact us using the information provided above. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing You with details of the information we hold about You.  
---|---  
8.3 | You may withdraw Your consent for us to process Your data at any time by notifying us in writing, but if you withdraw Your consent to certain types of processing described above we may be unable to maintain your membership of the Site.  
  9. Changes To Our Privacy Policy  9.1 | We reserve the right to make changes to the privacy policy from time to time. Any such changes to our privacy policy will be posted to the Site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.   
---|---
